Dear Hiring Manager,

I am writing to express my interest in the Process Expert role, which I came across through your web page. I feel a strong connection to the role and see many opportunities for mutual contribution that I would like to share with you.

With over a decade of experience as a consultant for leading technology and automation companies, I have successfully implemented solution strategies for process and infrastructure optimization across many industry verticals with high regulatory and security requirements.

My solid background, thanks to a continuous renewal of skills and contacts with the technology ecosystem, as well as my passion for innovation and my post-graduate in Digital Transformation of Organizations, make me a valuable resource for companies embracing the opportunities of the current digital revolution.

I invite you to review my CV, and will be happy to share with you how I am currently using these skills to help improve efficiency in process performance and patient satisfaction, through a digital transformation consultancy at Hospital Asepeyo Sant Cugat.

Thank you for your consideration. I look forward to the possibility of speaking with you soon.

Sincerely, Eduardo Pardo





Contact



http://es.linkedin.com/in/eduardpardo



epardo0908@gmail.com



(+34) 677 573 079



Barcelona (ability to telework)

Education

Barcelona School of Management (UPF) Postgraduate in digital transformation of organizations

EADA Business School Consultative Sales Management program

Universidad Politécnica Cataluña (UPC) Industrial engineering BS in automation

Skills

- Business Acumen (Adv)
- Problem Solving (Adv)
- Critical Thinking (Adv)
- Transversal Collaboration (Adv)
- Interpersonal Communication (Adv)
- **Decision Making**
- Agile Mindset & Practices

Expertise

Digital strategy | Industry 4.0 | IoT | Process optimization | Data integration | Power BI | RPA | No-Code UI Design | AWS/Azure Cloud | Cybersecurity | AI

Language

Fluent English Spanish, and Catalan native

Eduardo Pardo

Digital Solutions Consultant

Senior Consultant with extensive experience in process optimization across various industries and IT infrastructure. I thrive on understanding clients' needs and guiding them towards tailored solutions. With a people-centric approach, I drive continuous improvement, staying ahead of trends, and fostering strategic alliances

Experience

02/2017-09/2023 Latinia **Digital Solutions Consultant**

Led consulting services (4pax) in major national and Latin American banks, aligning their digital business strategy with the implementation of scalable, secure, cost-optimized solutions (with AWS, Azure, BI and RPA automation), achieving migrations without service interruption, increasing user profit through digital channels by 30% and reducing process and IT costs by 20%.

Managed all functional aspects of end to end solutions, including backend and frontend architecture, data and event integration, cybersecurity, planning, cost estimation and technology adoption in clients such as Sabadell, Santander, Banorte, Bancoppel, Redeban, among others.

Provided cross-functional support to Sales in pre-sales, and to DevOps, QA, PMs and SW Factoy during implementation and follow-up to ensure alignment with requirements.

04/2004-07/2016 Endress+Hauser | Abantia Sistemas & Telecom | Wonderware | Elecnor Sistemas **Digital Solutions Consultant**

Led the identification and successful implementation and adoption of digital strategies for clients in various industries, such as Almirall, Boehringer, Uriach, Puig, Coty, Nestle, Nutrexpa, Clariant, Unilever, Damm, and Borges.

Managed end to end digital solutions achieving improvements in process performance, customer engagement, energy efficiency, and savings in critical IT infrastructure, asset management, and inventory control, including consultancy services, software tools, hardware infrastructure, control systems, field and IoT sensors, ERP integration, engineering, commissioning and training.

Excelled in process analysis, solution architecture design, cost and planning management, demo creation, partner management, and presentations at national and international events.

09/2023 - 05/2024. Hospital Asepeyo Sant Cugat - Post-graduate in Digital Transformation - TFP Led consulting project on helping improve efficiency and patient satisfaction through analysis, process optimization, and end to end digital solutions at Hospital Asepeyo Sant Cugat.

02/2024 - 04/2024 IT Academy Power BI Course - Project

Analysis and rapport dashboards on modeling and efficient household consumption. Use of IoT, data connections (bills, electricity prices, weather, IoT meters), AWS resources (storage, RDS).

11/2016 – 04/2017 Imagine IoT program 'Dreamer'

Collaborated with dormity.com in the prototyping of an innovative IoT solution for sleep improvement. Presented the solution at a public event, showcasing expertise in sensor integration, cloud computing, mobile app development, and data analysis

Reference

Genis Roca D. Transf. Postgraduate Responsible

Hosp. Asepeyo StCugat Manager

Ernesto Luis Madrid

emadridmarcano@asepeyo.es

Joan Franco Abantia Sistemas & Telco Director comercial

Latinia CEO

consultingfranco@gmail.com

malcon@latinia.es

Marc Alcon

genisroca@gmail.com